

Milan Khimding

Kerabari-10, Morang Province 1 Nepal

E-mail: khimdingmilan99@gmail.com

Phone: 9862008082

SUMMARY

Introducing myself, I am a computer science student from Himalaya Darshan College. I have recently completed my four-year Bsc.csit bachelor. Through an intensive computer science course, I have acquired the required concept of programming to work as a web developer. I have work experience in Laravel Framework and some frontend.

WORK **EXPERIENCE** Techware Pvt. Ltd

Dec 2019 — Feb 2020

Intern

As web developer

K.U Academy

Mar 2016 — Sept 2016

Teacher

secondary level teaching

Techware Pvt Ltd

2020 — Present

Web Developer

worked on various projects

QUALIFICATIONS 1. I Have completed my Bachelor Degree in Bsc.Csit from Himalaya Darshan College in

Biratnagar.

2. I am working in IT company for more than 2 years.

EDUCATION

School

2010 - 2013

KU Academy

Gained initial schooling,

Kerabari, Morang

+2

2013 - 2015

Vishwa Adarsha College

Studied Science

Bachelor Degree

2016 - 2020

Himalaya Darshan College

Studied Computer Science and Information technology

SKILLS 1.Php Laravel framework

2.Vue Js

3.Bootstrap

4. Typescript 5.Javascript

6. Video Editing

7.Photoshop

PROJECTS 1.License Renewal Project

2. School Management System

3. Department of Water and Irrigation

4.Smart Veggie 5. Dairy Remainder

6. Restaurant Management System 7. Hospital Management System

8.Inventory

Computer Science and Information Technology Bachelor Degree ACHIEVEMENTS

Able to received Gandhi Scholarship for Secondary Level Study

AWARDS Gandhi Scholarship

2013 / Itahari

This program is conducted by Indian Government where they provide scholarship to few

students via conducting interviews. Luckily I got selected and got scholarship.

1. Graphic Designing ADDITIONAL

TRAINING AND

2020,Kerabari

COURSES This course was provided by ward commitiee of my hometown and was of 1 month

CONFERENCE 1. Digitalization Nepal

PARTICIPATION 2020 / Big Hotel / Biratnagar

Had chance to participate in conference where they talked about works that should be

carried out and challenges to make every part of Eastern Nepal digital.

LANGUAGES 1.English

2.Hindi

3.Nepali

Kapil Dahal REFERENCES

CEO of Techware Pvt.Ltd

9851196943

kapil4@gmail.com